<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:a10="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>US Drought Impact Reporter</title>
        <link>http://moderator.droughtreporter.unl.edu/rssfeed/</link>
        <description>Current Drought Impacts from the National Drought Mitigation Center's Drought Impact Reporter
        </description>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2018 15:54:14 -0600</lastBuildDate>
        <a10:id>DroughtImpactReporterRSSID</a10:id>
        <item>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">44187</guid>
            <link>http://moderator.droughtreporter.unl.edu/RSSfeed/ImpactView/44187</link>
            <title>Horsetail Fall not flowing in Yosemite National Park in California</title>
            <description>Yosemite’s Horsetail Fall may not have the firefall look as it often does in the latter part of
                February. The lack of snow meant that there was no water flowing to produce the waterfall.
                KFSN-TV ABC 30 Frenso/Visalia (Calif.), Feb. 12, 2018
            </description>
            <a10:updated>2018-02-15T10:53:02-06:00</a10:updated>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">44185</guid>
            <link>http://moderator.droughtreporter.unl.edu/RSSfeed/ImpactView/44185</link>
            <title>Wheat crop stunted in Cape Girardeau, Missouri</title>
            <description>Dry conditions slowed crop planting and crop emergence in Cape Girardeau County, according to a
                University of Missouri agronomy specialist. The wheat crop is shorter than that of one year ago, but is
                uniform. The crops were described as brown, stunted, and stressed, but the crops were still alive.
                Columbia Daily Tribune (Mo.), Feb. 12, 2018
            </description>
            <a10:updated>2018-02-14T15:52:34-06:00</a10:updated>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">44184</guid>
            <link>http://moderator.droughtreporter.unl.edu/RSSfeed/ImpactView/44184</link>
            <title>Winter feed depleted, rancher selling early in Tehama County, California</title>
            <description>Angus Cattle Ranching - Red Bluff CA. A lack of seasonal rains 2017-2018 has depleted our
                winter feed, and supplemental feed costs (alfalfa) have gone from $170/190 a ton to $260/280. We are
                selling early and cutting back on cows.
                From Tehama County, California, on February 14, 2018
            </description>
            <a10:updated>2018-02-14T15:38:00-06:00</a10:updated>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">44183</guid>
            <link>http://moderator.droughtreporter.unl.edu/RSSfeed/ImpactView/44183</link>
            <title>Resolution to extend burn ban in Major County, Oklahoma</title>
            <description>Major County commissioners passed a resolution to extend the county’s burn ban for 14 days with
                the intention of keeping a burn ban in place once Gov. Mary Fallin’s burn ban for 40 counties in western
                Oklahoma expired on Feb. 16.
                Enid News &amp; Eagle (Okla.), Feb. 12, 2018
            </description>
            <a10:updated>2018-02-14T13:41:37-06:00</a10:updated>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">44182</guid>
            <link>http://moderator.droughtreporter.unl.edu/RSSfeed/ImpactView/44182</link>
            <title>Watering plants, worried about pastures in Josephine County, Oregon</title>
            <description>We have had very little rain this calendar year. I am now hand watering the garden and have
                concerns that the pastures are now getting enough water. Our creek may be too low to use for irrigation
                this summer.
                CoCoRaHS Report from Station #Grants Pass 9.8 SSE on 2/12/2018
            </description>
            <a10:updated>2018-02-14T12:35:34-06:00</a10:updated>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">44181</guid>
            <link>http://moderator.droughtreporter.unl.edu/RSSfeed/ImpactView/44181</link>
            <title>Watering plants, hills not greening up much in San Diego County, California</title>
            <description>Last week was dry. No rain since Jan 19, and just 0.04" then. Still having to irrigate anything
                but drought-tolerant plants - quite unusual for this time of year. We've had many days of mild Santa Ana
                winds with humidities in the 20% range. Lots of dry vegetation which could support fire if it got
                started. Hillsides haven't turned green very much, as they usually do by February.
                CoCoRaHS Report from Station #La Mesa 2.6E on 2/12/2018
            </description>
            <a10:updated>2018-02-14T12:32:31-06:00</a10:updated>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">44180</guid>
            <link>http://moderator.droughtreporter.unl.edu/RSSfeed/ImpactView/44180</link>
            <title>Excessive number of water main breaks in Springfield, Illinois</title>
            <description>Springfield saw an exceptional 47 water main breaks during January 2018, setting a record for
                recent years. The high number of breaks was likely due to the extremely cold weather and dramatic
                temperature swings. Drought conditions may have also played a role.
                Springfield State Journal-Register (Ill.), Feb. 12, 2018
            </description>
            <a10:updated>2018-02-13T20:05:08-06:00</a10:updated>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">44179</guid>
            <link>http://moderator.droughtreporter.unl.edu/RSSfeed/ImpactView/44179</link>
            <title>Slim poppy crop at Antelope Valley California Poppy Reserve</title>
            <description>Only a few poppies came up at the Antelope Valley California Poppy Reserve in Lancaster, which
                does not bode well for the springtime wildflower bloom. The nearby hills were mostly brown.
                Los Angeles Times (Calif.), Feb. 13, 2018
            </description>
            <a10:updated>2018-02-13T19:22:30-06:00</a10:updated>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">44178</guid>
            <link>http://moderator.droughtreporter.unl.edu/RSSfeed/ImpactView/44178</link>
            <title>Wildflowers not poised for great bloom in California's Anza-Borrego Desert State Park</title>
            <description>Some flowers were blooming at Anza-Borrego Desert State Park, but even another half-inch of
                rain would do wonders, according to Betsy Knaak, executive director of the Anza-Borrego Desert Natural
                History Assn. Less than an inch of rain has fallen in Borrego Springs since the start of the year,
                compared to last year when around 4 ½ inches fell in January and February.
                Los Angeles Times (Calif.), Feb. 13, 2018
            </description>
            <a10:updated>2018-02-13T19:18:26-06:00</a10:updated>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">44177</guid>
            <link>http://moderator.droughtreporter.unl.edu/RSSfeed/ImpactView/44177</link>
            <title>Poor snowfall leaves ski resorts closed in California</title>
            <description>Royal Gorge, Tahoe Donner, TahoeXC and other Nordic trails were closed for skiing, as the poor
                snowpack left recreationists looking to mountain biking rather than skiing. The statewide snowpack for
                this time of year averaged 21 percent.
                Los Angeles Times (Calif.), Feb. 13, 2018
            </description>
            <a10:updated>2018-02-13T19:00:57-06:00</a10:updated>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">44174</guid>
            <link>http://moderator.droughtreporter.unl.edu/RSSfeed/ImpactView/44174</link>
            <title>California water board considering permanent water regulations</title>
            <description>The California State Water Resources Control Board was considering regulations that would make
                seven particular wasteful water practices a crime, including activities such as over watering lawns and
                irrigating street medians. The decision on the regulations is anticipated to occur at a Feb. 20 meeting.
                Orange County Register (Calif.), Feb. 12, 2018
            </description>
            <a10:updated>2018-02-13T17:03:48-06:00</a10:updated>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">44173</guid>
            <link>http://moderator.droughtreporter.unl.edu/RSSfeed/ImpactView/44173</link>
            <title>Fire crew preparations ahead of schedule in New Mexico</title>
            <description>Foreseeing an early start to the fire season, the U.S. Forest Service called up fire crews two
                to three weeks ahead of schedule for the spring fire season. Hot shot crews and firefighting aircraft
                were also asked to arrive early, according to Bill King, a fire management officer for the Santa Fe and
                Carson national forests.
                The Carson hot shot crew begins work on March 18, while the Santa Fe crew starts on April 1. A small,
                water-dropping helicopter will be on hand on April 1, one month ahead of schedule.
                Santa Fe New Mexican (N.M.), Feb. 12, 2018
            </description>
            <a10:updated>2018-02-13T16:03:19-06:00</a10:updated>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">44172</guid>
            <link>http://moderator.droughtreporter.unl.edu/RSSfeed/ImpactView/44172</link>
            <title>Poor wheat growth in Garfield County, Oklahoma</title>
            <description>Producers in Garfield County have not received significant precipitation in three months,
                leaving wheat pasture unable to provide much grazing for livestock. Due to the persistent drought, some
                producers were considering switching from wheat to another crop for the year, according to Josh Bushong,
                Oklahoma Cooperative Extension Service northwest area agronomy specialist.
                Producers were waiting to topdress their fields with nitrogen, but need rain after the application to
                incorporate it into the field to be most effective.
                Enid News &amp; Eagle (Okla.), Feb. 4, 2018
            </description>
            <a10:updated>2018-02-13T14:51:03-06:00</a10:updated>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">44171</guid>
            <link>http://moderator.droughtreporter.unl.edu/RSSfeed/ImpactView/44171</link>
            <title>Skiing on man-made snow in Taos County, New Mexico</title>
            <description>We have had warm weather and no significant rainfall. Bare ground in dry to several inches. A
                lot of fear for spring fires since the mountains have essentially no snow cover. The Taos Ski Valley is
                skiing on man-made snow.

                CoCoRaHS Report from Station #Arroyo Seco 1.4 E on 2/12/2018
            </description>
            <a10:updated>2018-02-13T13:58:22-06:00</a10:updated>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">44170</guid>
            <link>http://moderator.droughtreporter.unl.edu/RSSfeed/ImpactView/44170</link>
            <title>Bird activity increasing in Aitkin County, Minnesota</title>
            <description>Dry cold pattern continued this week. Bird activity continues to increase at my feeders both in
                number and variety. If forecast proves true, this will likely be the peak of the cold weather effects
                today as warming to begin after today. I will likely move into the severely dry soon if dry pattern
                continues through the loss of snow.

                CoCoRaHS Report from Station #Tamarack 1.4 SW on 2/12/2018
            </description>
            <a10:updated>2018-02-13T13:17:28-06:00</a10:updated>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">44175</guid>
            <link>http://moderator.droughtreporter.unl.edu/RSSfeed/ImpactView/44175</link>
            <title>Snowfall hurting skiing in Lincoln County, New Mexico</title>
            <description>Ski Apache has recorded just 24 inches of snow more than halfway through the ski season, which
                is far below the 300 inches received during the 2010 season, according to the director of operations for
                the resort. Despite being able to make artificial snow, the ski area only has six of 54 lanes open for
                use.
                KVIA-TV ABC 7 El Paso (Texas), Feb. 8, 2018
            </description>
            <a10:updated>2018-02-13T00:00:00-06:00</a10:updated>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">44176</guid>
            <link>http://moderator.droughtreporter.unl.edu/RSSfeed/ImpactView/44176</link>
            <title>Business down at ski shop in Alto, New Mexico</title>
            <description>Business was down 75 percent at Alto Ski Shop. The owner intends to try to keep the shop open
                until spring break, despite having so few customers.
                KVIA-TV ABC 7 El Paso (Texas), Feb. 8, 2018
            </description>
            <a10:updated>2018-02-13T00:00:00-06:00</a10:updated>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">44169</guid>
            <link>http://moderator.droughtreporter.unl.edu/RSSfeed/ImpactView/44169</link>
            <title>Dry weather hindering farm work in Lubbock County, Texas</title>
            <description>A cotton grower and his crew near Lubbock were having trouble keeping busy because the dry
                weather was preventing them from accomplishing tasks. Many farmers were wanting to tillage plow, turn
                the soil and add fertilizer, but the hard, dry topsoil could hurt the equipment and the soil would blow
                away on a windy day.
                Lubbock Avalanche-Journal (Texas), Feb. 10, 2018
            </description>
            <a10:updated>2018-02-12T17:21:23-06:00</a10:updated>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">44168</guid>
            <link>http://moderator.droughtreporter.unl.edu/RSSfeed/ImpactView/44168</link>
            <title>Burn ban in effect in Johnston County, Oklahoma</title>
            <description>We are in burn ban, only trace rain this am, last week had light rain freeze on contact, pray
                for rain and temp. above 32F temp. @ report 29F

                CoCoRaHS Report from Station #Coleman 4.6 WNW on 2/10/2018
            </description>
            <a10:updated>2018-02-12T17:11:09-06:00</a10:updated>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">44167</guid>
            <link>http://moderator.droughtreporter.unl.edu/RSSfeed/ImpactView/44167</link>
            <title>Watering drought-tolerant landscaping in Socorro County, New Mexico</title>
            <description>128 days without ANY moisture. Have not heard reports from
                Elephant Butte but ABQ recommending watering plants once a week. already and I will be watering xeric
                yard biweekly now. Fire danger high.
                CoCoRaHS Report from Station #San Antonio 0.7 SSW on 2/10/2018
            </description>
            <a10:updated>2018-02-12T16:50:58-06:00</a10:updated>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">44165</guid>
            <link>http://moderator.droughtreporter.unl.edu/RSSfeed/ImpactView/44165</link>
            <title>Trees suffering from lack of rain in Mariposa County, California</title>
            <description>Hardly a drop of rain. The trees are suffering from lack of water and again an onslaught of
                bark beetles. Even the natural plants are suffering. There will be fire again.
                CoCoRaHS Report from Station #Mariposa 3.7 NNW on 2/10/2018
            </description>
            <a10:updated>2018-02-12T16:47:41-06:00</a10:updated>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">44164</guid>
            <link>http://moderator.droughtreporter.unl.edu/RSSfeed/ImpactView/44164</link>
            <title>Birds and wildlife seeking water in El Paso County, Texas</title>
            <description>Increasing the frequency of irrigation given nearly no rain at all to date this year. Birds and
                other wildlife (foxes) using water bowls constantly. Feeder literally covered with birds much of the
                day.
                CoCoRaHS Report from Station #El Paso 5.1 SW on 2/11/2018
            </description>
            <a10:updated>2018-02-12T16:16:49-06:00</a10:updated>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">44163</guid>
            <link>http://moderator.droughtreporter.unl.edu/RSSfeed/ImpactView/44163</link>
            <title>Ponds are low and burn ban imposed in Denton County, Texas</title>
            <description>Have had several significant wildfires within 5 miles. The County has imposed a burn ban. Most
                tanks (ponds) are at less than half of their normal levels. Some have dried up.

                CoCoRaHS Report from Station #Sanger 5.4 NW on 2/9/2018
            </description>
            <a10:updated>2018-02-12T15:26:29-06:00</a10:updated>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">44162</guid>
            <link>http://moderator.droughtreporter.unl.edu/RSSfeed/ImpactView/44162</link>
            <title>Hay and feed supplies strained in Clay, Jack, and Montague counties in Texas</title>
            <description>This fall I did not have any wheat to graze and it looks like wheat crop is going to be a total
                loss. With this ongoing issue it is putting a strain on my hay supply and feed. This will also affect my
                spring hay supply.
                From Montague County, Texas, on February 10, 2018
            </description>
            <a10:updated>2018-02-12T14:47:03-06:00</a10:updated>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">44161</guid>
            <link>http://moderator.droughtreporter.unl.edu/RSSfeed/ImpactView/44161</link>
            <title>Livestock may have to relocate due to no moisture in Sierra County, New Mexico</title>
            <description>We are having to feed everyday it has never been this dry. We have no water left in the tanks
                and the dust it terrible. If we don't get some rain soon, we'll have to find a rent place to move
                livestock.

                CoCoRaHS Report from Station #Cuchillo 2.2 S on 2/9/2018
            </description>
            <a10:updated>2018-02-12T14:21:32-06:00</a10:updated>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">44160</guid>
            <link>http://moderator.droughtreporter.unl.edu/RSSfeed/ImpactView/44160</link>
            <title>Hay being fed to cattle in Sierra County, New Mexico</title>
            <description>We have had no moisture at all. The tanks are all dried up, the roads are dust 6 inches deep.
                My cattle have zero feed, I am feeding hay everyday to keep them alive. It's terribly dry, we need some
                moisture so hopefully we can get some tumble weeds to survive this spring.

                CoCoRaHS Report from Station #Cuchillo 1.1 ESE on 2/9/2018
            </description>
            <a10:updated>2018-02-12T14:17:22-06:00</a10:updated>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">44166</guid>
            <link>http://moderator.droughtreporter.unl.edu/RSSfeed/ImpactView/44166</link>
            <title>Burning restrictions in place in Newton County, Missouri</title>
            <description>Continued dry with high fire danger, although we have had some very light precipitation in the
                last week, it has not given appreciable relief. Shoal Creek is low and wildlife is seeking forage and
                water around village. This is a very cold, dry winter winter for this area. Outside burning restrictions
                are in place.

                CoCoRaHS Report from Station #Shoal Creek Estates 0.2 SE on 2/10/2018
            </description>
            <a10:updated>2018-02-12T00:00:00-06:00</a10:updated>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">44159</guid>
            <link>http://moderator.droughtreporter.unl.edu/RSSfeed/ImpactView/44159</link>
            <title>Late fall-planted crops struggling near Wichita Falls, Texas</title>
            <description>Late-planted crops near Wichita Falls needed rain badly and have not been able to withstand the
                dry conditions well because their root systems were not well-developed enough to reach deep and tap into
                moisture.
                KFDX NBC 3- KJTL FOX 18 - KJBO MyTV 35 (Wichita Falls, Texas), Feb. 8, 2018
            </description>
            <a10:updated>2018-02-09T19:02:44-06:00</a10:updated>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">44158</guid>
            <link>http://moderator.droughtreporter.unl.edu/RSSfeed/ImpactView/44158</link>
            <title>Extra firefighters undergoing training in New Mexico</title>
            <description>New Mexico State Forestry has already begun to train extra firefighters to be prepared when the
                calls for assistance begin. Members of the fire crews were doing their physical fitness testing and
                getting their equipment ready.
                KRQE-TV CBS 13 (Albuquerque, N.M.), Feb. 8, 2018
            </description>
            <a10:updated>2018-02-09T18:57:58-06:00</a10:updated>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">44157</guid>
            <link>http://moderator.droughtreporter.unl.edu/RSSfeed/ImpactView/44157</link>
            <title>Drought may contribute to rabies danger in southern Arizona</title>
            <description>Given the number of rabies cases in southern Arizona among foxes in recent months, pet owners
                were warned to get their pets vaccinated and not to feed wildlife. The drought severity makes county
                officials anticipate an increase in wildlife-human interaction, which may pose a threat to human health.
                Tucson News Now (Ariz.), Feb. 8, 2018
            </description>
            <a10:updated>2018-02-09T18:42:49-06:00</a10:updated>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">44156</guid>
            <link>http://moderator.droughtreporter.unl.edu/RSSfeed/ImpactView/44156</link>
            <title>More snow needed to reopen skiing at Mt. Ashland in Oregon</title>
            <description>Skiing at Mt. Ashland was at an end until further notice, pending additional snowfall. The ski
                area opened late, due to a dearth of snow.
                Klamath Falls Herald and News (Ore.), Feb. 9, 2018
            </description>
            <a10:updated>2018-02-09T18:32:57-06:00</a10:updated>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">44153</guid>
            <link>http://moderator.droughtreporter.unl.edu/RSSfeed/ImpactView/44153</link>
            <title>Drought diminished seasonal waterfall in Douglas County, Oregon</title>
            <description>Have a seasonal waterfall on property. It has only run for two days so far this winter. Usually
                starts in December and runs solid until April.
                CoCoRaHS Report from Station #Roseburg 4.5 WSW on 2/8/2018
            </description>
            <a10:updated>2018-02-09T16:48:00-06:00</a10:updated>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">44152</guid>
            <link>http://moderator.droughtreporter.unl.edu/RSSfeed/ImpactView/44152</link>
            <title>High water bill in Riverside County, California</title>
            <description>Abnormally dry making a unseasonably high water bill.
                CoCoRaHS Report from Station #San Jacinto 4.2 W on 2/8/2018
            </description>
            <a10:updated>2018-02-09T16:45:48-06:00</a10:updated>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">44151</guid>
            <link>http://moderator.droughtreporter.unl.edu/RSSfeed/ImpactView/44151</link>
            <title>Farmers hauling water for cattle in McDonald County, Missouri</title>
            <description>Ponds are drying up some neighbors are hauling water for their cattle less than 6 inches or
                rain since 1 Sept 17.
                CoCoRaHS Report from Station #Anderson 6.8 W on 2/8/2018
            </description>
            <a10:updated>2018-02-09T16:43:08-06:00</a10:updated>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">44149</guid>
            <link>http://moderator.droughtreporter.unl.edu/RSSfeed/ImpactView/44149</link>
            <title>Dry conditions in the are causing fire and bad conditions for skiing in Navajo County, Arizona
            </title>
            <description>forest fire (Eagle Nest Fire)close by. Ski conditions horrible due to lack of snow lake levels
                lowering.

                CoCoRaHS Report from Station #Pinetop-Lakeside 1.4 NNW on 2/8/2018
            </description>
            <a10:updated>2018-02-09T14:37:49-06:00</a10:updated>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">44150</guid>
            <link>http://moderator.droughtreporter.unl.edu/RSSfeed/ImpactView/44150</link>
            <title>Fire danger creates burn ban in Eastland County, Texas</title>
            <description>Have not received rain of any significant amount since. 12/22/2017. We have extreme fire danger
                in this area. Vegetation is very dry. Water tanks are drying up. Burn ban in effect.

                CoCoRaHS Report from Station #Cisco 4.1 N on 2/8/2018
            </description>
            <a10:updated>2018-02-09T00:00:00-06:00</a10:updated>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">44155</guid>
            <link>http://moderator.droughtreporter.unl.edu/RSSfeed/ImpactView/44155</link>
            <title>Chemult Sled Dog races canceled for lack of snow in Lake County, Oregon</title>
            <description>The annual Chemult Sled Dog races to be held in January were canceled due to low snowpack.
                Klamath Falls Herald and News (Ore.), Feb. 9, 2018
            </description>
            <a10:updated>2018-02-09T00:00:00-06:00</a10:updated>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">44154</guid>
            <link>http://moderator.droughtreporter.unl.edu/RSSfeed/ImpactView/44154</link>
            <title>Ski area in Lake County, Oregon to remain closed for winter season</title>
            <description>Operators of Warner Canyon Ski Area opted to remain closed for the entire winter season, given
                that they have been unable to open thus far for lack of snow. The ski area typically opens the last week
                of December and remains open as long as the snow lasts.
                Klamath Falls Herald and News (Ore.), Feb. 9, 2018
            </description>
            <a10:updated>2018-02-09T00:00:00-06:00</a10:updated>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">44148</guid>
            <link>http://moderator.droughtreporter.unl.edu/RSSfeed/ImpactView/44148</link>
            <title>Arizona governor seeking more funds for wildfire prevention</title>
            <description>Gov. Doug Ducey of Arizona asked the Legislature to increase funding for fire prevention
                efforts from an annual figure of $1 million to $2 million. The additional funds would be used to remove
                brush and other fuels loads since drought has dramatically increased the fire danger.
                KVOA-TV NBC 4 Tucson (Ariz.), Feb. 8, 2018
            </description>
            <a10:updated>2018-02-08T18:53:13-06:00</a10:updated>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">44146</guid>
            <link>http://moderator.droughtreporter.unl.edu/RSSfeed/ImpactView/44146</link>
            <title>Irrigating winter crops, dust control for roads in Fresno County, California</title>
            <description>1.76 inches of rain since July 1, 2017. Irrigating winter crops and watering down roads for
                dust control during what should be our wettest season.
                CoCoRaHS Report from Station #Helm 2.7 NNE on 2/7/2018
            </description>
            <a10:updated>2018-02-08T13:06:17-06:00</a10:updated>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">44145</guid>
            <link>http://moderator.droughtreporter.unl.edu/RSSfeed/ImpactView/44145</link>
            <title>Drought turning cacti, trees brown in Pima County, Arizona</title>
            <description>Cactus and trees all turning brown with no rain.
                CoCoRaHS Report from Station #Three Points 2.9 S on 2/7/2018
            </description>
            <a10:updated>2018-02-08T13:02:19-06:00</a10:updated>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">44144</guid>
            <link>http://moderator.droughtreporter.unl.edu/RSSfeed/ImpactView/44144</link>
            <title>Soil too hard for gardening in Sandoval County, New Mexico</title>
            <description>Only .12" of rain since October. Top 6" of soil v. dry. Cannot turn the compost into the garden
                because the soil is too hard.
                CoCoRaHS Report from Station #Corrales 1.3 ENE on 2/7/2018
            </description>
            <a10:updated>2018-02-08T12:57:06-06:00</a10:updated>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">44143</guid>
            <link>http://moderator.droughtreporter.unl.edu/RSSfeed/ImpactView/44143</link>
            <title>Burn ban in place in Hays County, Texas</title>
            <description>It has been over 50 days since the last rainfall that produced any runoff. The flow of the
                Blanco River at RR12 remains below the 90-year median and was 21cfs at Fisher Store bridge. A burn ban
                is in place.

                CoCoRaHS Report from Station #Wimberley 4.0 WSW on 2/7/2018
            </description>
            <a10:updated>2018-02-08T11:43:19-06:00</a10:updated>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">44142</guid>
            <link>http://moderator.droughtreporter.unl.edu/RSSfeed/ImpactView/44142</link>
            <title>Supplemental feeding needed for stock in Val Verde County, Texas</title>
            <description>Winter rains did not come this year....so far. Supplemental feeding required for stock.

                CoCoRaHS Report from Station #Comstock 29.7 NW on 2/7/2018
            </description>
            <a10:updated>2018-02-08T11:29:20-06:00</a10:updated>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">44141</guid>
            <link>http://moderator.droughtreporter.unl.edu/RSSfeed/ImpactView/44141</link>
            <title>Dryness slowed development of winter wheat in Kit Carson County, Colorado</title>
            <description>Slowing development of winter wheat.
                CoCoRaHS Report from Station #Vona 6.5 SSW on 2/6/2018
            </description>
            <a10:updated>2018-02-07T14:51:11-06:00</a10:updated>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">44140</guid>
            <link>http://moderator.droughtreporter.unl.edu/RSSfeed/ImpactView/44140</link>
            <title>Dry enough to water cactus in Grant County, New Mexico</title>
            <description>Dry enough that we are watering the cactus once a month. Not much snow pack if any in the local
                area.
                CoCoRaHS Report from Station #Silver City 2.6 NNW on 2/6/2018
            </description>
            <a10:updated>2018-02-07T14:46:09-06:00</a10:updated>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">44139</guid>
            <link>http://moderator.droughtreporter.unl.edu/RSSfeed/ImpactView/44139</link>
            <title>Grass fires have been occurring in Walworth County, Wisconsin</title>
            <description>Just responded to two grass fire incidents on Feb 3 due to the lack of snow cover. Dry surface
                conditions have now eased due to recent snowfall.

                CoCoRaHS Report from Station #Mukwonago 3.4 SW on 2/6/2018
            </description>
            <a10:updated>2018-02-07T14:01:53-06:00</a10:updated>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">44137</guid>
            <link>http://moderator.droughtreporter.unl.edu/RSSfeed/ImpactView/44137</link>
            <title>Bermuda grass is dead and other plants not doing well in Lubbock County, Texas</title>
            <description>No rain for 5 months. Even Bermuda grass is dead and all pieces get tracked into the house.
                Leaves so dry the disintegrate when stepped on. Plant buds appear dried up, not succulent as would
                normally be so that they might open when the warm temperatures come. Pecan trees in the neighborhood
                have pecans that have shriveled fruit inside.

                CoCoRaHS Report from Station #Lubbock 3.0 S on 2/6/2018
            </description>
            <a10:updated>2018-02-07T13:50:07-06:00</a10:updated>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">44136</guid>
            <link>http://moderator.droughtreporter.unl.edu/RSSfeed/ImpactView/44136</link>
            <title>Energy costs are increasing and some activities are being canceled in Pembina County, North Dakota
            </title>
            <description>Conditions remain the same as last report. No snow in precipitation. We've had strong winds
                from NW and SE causing blowing dirt where you cannot see in open areas. We had about 1/2 of snow which
                helped last Friday but rest of week was blowing dirt. Dirt being tracked in everywhere. Cold persists
                with wind chills. Some outdoor events have been canceled do to no snow. Cold been tough on the deer.
                Taking lots of fuel oil to warm the house. Energy costs are high.

                CoCoRaHS Report from Station #Cavalier 7.9 WNW on 2/6/2018
            </description>
            <a10:updated>2018-02-07T13:45:03-06:00</a10:updated>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">44135</guid>
            <link>http://moderator.droughtreporter.unl.edu/RSSfeed/ImpactView/44135</link>
            <title>Plants stressed, water in short supply in Monterey County, California</title>
            <description>Water shortage, plants stressed, no water for irrigation.
                CoCoRaHS Report from Station #Cambria 27.2 NW on 2/6/2018
            </description>
            <a10:updated>2018-02-07T12:03:44-06:00</a10:updated>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>