<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<source>
    <category id="1">
        <topic>Wastewater</topic>
        <items>
            <item>
                <link>https://water.usgs.gov/edu/wuww.html</link>
                <title>Wastewater Treatment Water Use</title>
                <description>
                    We consider wastewater treatment as a water use because it is so interconnected with the other uses of water.
                    Much of the water used by homes, industries, and businesses must be treated before it is released back to
                    the environment. If the term "wastewater treatment" is confusing to you, you might think of it as "sewage treatment."
                    Nature has an amazing ability to cope with small amounts of water wastes and pollution, but it would be
                    overwhelmed if we didn't treat the billions of gallons of wastewater and sewage produced every day before
                    releasing it back to the environment. Treatment plants reduce pollutants in wastewater to a level
                    nature can handle.
                </description>
                <updated>2016-02-14T15:52:34-06:00</updated>
            </item>
            <item>
                <link>http://www.lubbockonline.com/article/20160608/NEWS/306089912</link>
                <title>Where it goes when you flush: Another sewage plant in the works</title>
                <description>Many of the city’s long-term water goals laid out in the Lubbock 2013 Strategic Water Supply
                    Plan call for some type of wastewater reuse system. The city has rights to the treated wastewater
                    it pumps into the Brazos River tributary of the Yellow House Canyon System that flows through the north and east
                    sides of the city, so the idea is to catch and treat that water for use again in city taps.
                </description>
                <updated>2016-06-08T15:52:34-06:00</updated>
            </item>
            <item>
                <link>https://www.conserve-energy-future.com/process-of-wastewater-treatment.php</link>
                <title>What is Wastewater Treatment?</title>
                <description>Wastewater treatment is the process of converting wastewater – water that is no longer
                    needed or is no longer suitable for use – into bilge water that can be discharged back into the environment.
                    It’s formed by a number of activities including bathing, washing, using the toilet, and rainwater runoff.
                    Wastewater is full of contaminants including bacteria, chemicals and other toxins. Its treatment aims at
                    reducing the contaminants to acceptable levels to make the water safe for discharge back into
                    the environment.
                </description>
                <updated>2018-02-14T15:52:34-06:00</updated>
            </item>
            <item>
                <link>http://www.nyc.gov/html/dep/html/wastewater/wwsystem-process.shtml</link>
                <title>New York City's Wastewater Treatment System</title>
                <description>Every day, wastewater goes down toilets and drains in homes, schools, businesses and factories and then
                    flows into New York City's sewer system. Runoff from rain and melting snow, street and sidewalk washing,
                    and other outdoor activities flows into catchbasins in the streets and from there into the sewers. In some
                    New York City neighborhoods, runoff from the streets is carried by separate storm sewers directly
                    to local streams, rivers and bays. In most areas of the City, sanitary and industrial wastewater,
                    rainwater and street runoff are collected in the same sewers and then conveyed together to the City's treatment plants.
                    This is known as a combined sewer system. Sometimes, during heavy rains or snow, combined sewers
                    fill to capacity and are unable to carry the combined sanitary and storm sewage to the plants.When this
                    occurs the mix of excess storm water and untreated sewage flows directly into the City's waterways.
                    This is called combined sewer overflow (CSO). Approximately 70 percent of the City sewers are combined.
                </description>
                <updated>2018-02-14T15:52:34-06:00</updated>
            </item>
        </items>
    </category>
    <category id="2">
        <topic>Industrial water</topic>
        <items>
            <item>
                <link>https://www.samcotech.com/what-is-an-industrial-water-treatment-system-process/</link>
                <title>What Is an Industrial Water Treatment System and How Does It Work?</title>
                <description>Industrial water treatment systems meet a variety of purification and separation needs.
                    They can range from relatively compact and straightforward to complex, multiunit processes that serve a
                    variety of applications. If you’re new to water treatment, you might be asking “What is an industrial water
                    treatment system and how does it work?”
                </description>
                <updated>2017-09-29T15:52:34-06:00</updated>
            </item>

            <item>
                <link>https://www.veoliawatertechnologies.com/en/our-expertise/industrial</link>
                <title>Industrial water treatment</title>
                <description>Veolia Water Technologies is one of the most innovative industrial water treatment companies.
                    We create and implement tailored or standardized industrial water treatment solutions and industrial
                    wastewater treatment systems. Our industrial engineers combine their expertise with years of operational experience
                    in the water/wastewater, steam and power sectors, allowing clients to focus on their core businesses.
                </description>
                <updated>2017-09-29T15:52:34-06:00</updated>
            </item>

            <item>
                <link>https://www.thomasnet.com/southern-texas/water-treatment-services-92970953-1.html</link>
                <title>Water Treatment Services serving Southern Texas</title>
                <description>Process water analysis lab treatment services. Polyphosphate and orthophosphate blends, bleaches,
                    low freeze caustic chemicals, formulations and de-scaling analysis can be done. Used for analyzing in discoloration,
                    excess metals and scale issue applications. Capability focuses include turnkey, high volume production,
                    packaging and custom formulation. Additional services such as reverse engineering, warehousing, inspection and
                    testing are offered. 7-10 working days lead time for water analysis
                </description>
                <updated>2017-09-29T15:52:34-06:00</updated>
            </item>

        </items>
    </category>
     <category id="3">
        <topic>Domestic water</topic>
        <items>
            <item>
                <link>https://www.ecowaterlubbock.com/products/drinking-water-system</link>
                <title>DRINKING WATER SYSTEMS</title>
                <description>The quality of your home’s water may meet local standards, but it might not meet your own.
                    Ordinary tap water can contain dissolved metals, including lead and iron. It might contain nitrates,
                    chlorine and mineral salts. Your tap water could also contain other undesirable substances such as sulfates,
                    mercury, asbestos and arsenic.
                </description>
                <updated>2018-02-14T15:52:34-06:00</updated>
            </item>
            <item>
                <link>https://agwt.org/content/domestic-water-treatment-homeowners</link>
                <title>Domestic Water Treatment for Homeowners</title>
                <description>The American Ground Water Trust has prepared this consumer information pamphlet to help people
                    make good economic and environmental decisions about water treatment. There are many water supply
                    specialists who provide water supply products and services; this pamphlet will assist you to
                    obtain the professional help you need.
                </description>
                <updated>2018-02-14T15:52:34-06:00</updated>
            </item>

            <item>
                <link>http://hyperfilteration.in/filteration-method/domestic-water-treatment</link>
                <title>Domestic Water Treatment</title>
                <description>Domestic water or drinking water/ potable water should be completely safe and free from any
                    harmful effect on users; It must be pleasant on tongue [ palatable ], be free of colour, odour,
                    turbidity and should have permitted level of dissolved solids such as Calcium Magnesium, sodium,
                    their bicarbonates, chlorides and sulphates. Water for laundry, lavatories, baths etc. - If water is hard,
                    it will not form lather with soap and clothes shall not be washed clean and bright. When it comes to drinking water,
                    water with certain level of hardness may be OK, but the same hard water will clog and scale the GI pipes,
                    heaters, geysers for the reason that some of the dissolved solids like Calcium Carbonate and Magnecium Hydroxide
                    have lower solubility in water and with rise of temperature, they will precipitate out.
                </description>
                <updated>2018-02-14T15:52:34-06:00</updated>
            </item>

            <item>
                <link>https://www.perfectwater.ie/domestic-water-purification-systems/</link>
                <title>Domestic Water Purification Systems</title>
                <description>Perfect Water Systems was established in 1995 and is based in Charleville, County Cork, Ireland.
                    Through our attention to detail and quality home installations, we have gained a reputation for our
                    high quality work and professional after-care service. We promise a complete and perfect water treatment service
                    to both our home and commercial customers. We are distributors in Ireland for Kinetico domestic and home
                    water purification systems and specialise in the sale, installation and servicing of both Kinetico
                    and competitor water treatment systems.
                </description>
                <updated>2018-02-14T15:52:34-06:00</updated>
            </item>
        </items>
    </category>
</source>