<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<source>
    <category id="1">
        <topic>Bottled water processing</topic>
        <items>
            <item>
                <link>https://www.freedrinkingwater.com/water-education3/31-water-bottled-water-purification-process.htm</link>
                <title>The Bottled Water Purification Process</title>
                <description>A trip to the local grocery store and a walk down the beverage aisle will reveal dozens of
                    varieties of bottled water. From big, two gallon jugs with spouts to mini bottles that can fit in a lunch box,
                    there are kinds galore. But many may take for granted to process that takes place to get that water from the source,
                    safely into the bottle and into our lives.
                </description>
                <updated>2018-02-14T15:52:34-06:00</updated>
            </item>
            <item>
                <link>https://www.drinkmorewater.com/water-bottling</link>
                <title>Bottling Process &amp; Tour</title>
                <description>Welcome to our bottling plant!! While pictures don’t really do it justice, we’ve assembled
                    a few photos to give you an idea of how the whole thing works. We start with racks of empty bottles
                    collected by our route managers. When they pick up your bottles at your home or office, they inspect
                    each of them for cleanliness and put them into these blue racks. Once the racks arrive at the bottling line,
                    the bottles are again inspected visually and the each bottle is sniffed for any foreign contaminants.
                    Once a bottle passes these inspections, it is loaded onto the washer conveyor.
                </description>
                <updated>2018-02-14T15:52:34-06:00</updated>
            </item>
            <item>
                <link>http://moderator.droughtreporter.unl.edu/RSSfeed/ImpactView/44185</link>
                <title>Wheat crop stunted in Cape Girardeau, Missouri</title>
                <description>Dry conditions slowed crop planting and crop emergence in Cape Girardeau County, according to a
                    University of Missouri agronomy specialist. The wheat crop is shorter than that of one year ago, but is
                    uniform. The crops were described as brown, stunted, and stressed, but the crops were still alive.
                    Columbia Daily Tribune (Mo.), Feb. 12, 2018
                </description>
                <updated>2018-02-14T15:52:34-06:00</updated>
            </item>
            <item>
                <link>https://www.nestle-waters.com/creating-shared-value/environmental-performance/manufacturing</link>
                <title>Bottled water production</title>
                <description>The bottled water industry involves a relatively light manufacturing process, meaning it does not
                    require any heavy transformation processes. Impacts considered in the manufacturing phase are primarily related to
                    energy required for the entire production process at the factory level. This includes the transformation of packaging
                    materials into bottles, product bottling (pumping, storage, treatments (if any), filling), securing with secondary
                    packaging and storage until finished products are shipped outside of the factory.
                </description>
                <updated>2018-02-14T15:52:34-06:00</updated>
            </item>
            <item>
                <link>https://www.bottledwater.org/education/bottled-water-production</link>
                <title>BOTTLED WATER PRODUCTION</title>
                <description>All bottled water products - whether from groundwater or public water sources - are produced
                    utilizing a multi-barrier approach. From source to finished product, a multi-barrier approach helps prevent
                    possible harmful contamination to the finished product as well as storage,
                    production, and transportation equipment. Many of the steps in a multi-barrier system are effective in
                    safeguarding bottled water from microbiological and other contamination.
                </description>
                <updated>2018-02-14T15:52:34-06:00</updated>
            </item>
        </items>
    </category>
    <category id="2">
        <topic>Purified water</topic>
        <items>
            <item>
                <link>https://www.nestle-waters.com/brands/water-quality/purified-water</link>
                <title>Purified water : the 12 steps quality process</title>
                <description>Below are the 12 steps of the quality process Nestlé Waters uses to produce NESTLÉ PURE LIFE in North America.
                    A significant share of our product portfolio in our emerging markets and in the United States is made
                    up of purified water or prepared water. More precisions about our categories of water.
                </description>
                <updated>2015-02-14T15:52:34-06:00</updated>
            </item>
            <item>
                <link>https://www.cdc.gov/healthywater/drinking/nutrition/index.html</link>
                <title>Water &amp; Nutrition</title>
                <description>Getting enough water every day is important for your health. Healthy people meet their fluid
                    needs by drinking when thirsty and drinking with meals. Most of your fluid needs are met through the
                    water and beverages you drink. However, you can get some fluids through the foods that you eat. For example,
                    broth soups and foods with high water content such as celery, tomatoes, or melons can contribute to fluid intake.
                </description>
                <updated>2015-02-14T15:52:34-06:00</updated>
            </item>
            <item>
                <link>http://moderator.droughtreporter.unl.edu/RSSfeed/ImpactView/44185</link>
                <title>Wheat crop stunted in Cape Girardeau, Missouri</title>
                <description>Dry conditions slowed crop planting and crop emergence in Cape Girardeau County, according to a
                    University of Missouri agronomy specialist. The wheat crop is shorter than that of one year ago, but is
                    uniform. The crops were described as brown, stunted, and stressed, but the crops were still alive.
                    Columbia Daily Tribune (Mo.), Feb. 12, 2018
                </description>
                <updated>2018-02-14T15:52:34-06:00</updated>
            </item>
        </items>
    </category>
     <category id="3">
        <topic>Recreational water</topic>
        <items>

            <item>
                <link>https://www.aquafineuv.com/Recreational-Water</link>
                <title>Recreational Water</title>
                <description>For both public and private pools and splash water parks, disinfection plays a key role as a required treatment step.
                    Swimming pool water must undergo treatment in order to remain free of harmful substances, bacteria, viruses,
                    algae and other pathogens to be suitable for use by swimmers. Of particular concern in swimming pool waters
                    are the formation of chloramines and chlorinated organic compounds that are known to give rise to
                    swimming pool smell and eye, nose and throat irritation. For most pool operators, chlorine is the disinfectant of choice,
                    although there is growing awareness regarding the negative health effects of chlorine and its by-products.
                    On the other hand, unlike bacterial pathogens, Cryptosporidium oocysts are resistant to chlorine disinfection and
                    can survive for days in treated recreational water venues.
                </description>
                <updated>2018-02-14T15:52:34-06:00</updated>
            </item>

            <item>
                <link>https://www.epa.gov/wqc/microbial-pathogenrecreational-water-quality-criteria</link>
                <title>Microbial (Pathogen)/Recreational Water Quality Criteria</title>
                <description>EPA develops criteria to protect people from microbial organisms (sometimes referred to as pathogens)
                    such as bacteria and viruses in water bodies (e.g., lakes, rivers, beaches).  Pathogens can make our waters unsafe for humans.
                    Swimming and other recreational activities in water contaminated with pathogens can make people ill. People can also become
                    exposed by drinking untreated water from contaminated water bodies.
                </description>
                <updated>2018-02-14T15:52:34-06:00</updated>
            </item>

            <item>
                <link>https://www.wqpmag.com/recreational-water-treatment-emerging-threat</link>
                <title>RECREATIONAL WATER TREATMENT: AN EMERGING THREAT</title>
                <description>Outbreaks of illness associated with recreational water in the U.S. continue to rise, according to a
                    June 2015 Morbidity and Mortality Weekly Report from the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC).
                    The report covers illness outbreaks across the U.S., identifying source (treated versus untreated water) and etiology,
                    or cause. The numbers presented are likely just the tip of the iceberg, however, as they are generally regarded as
                    an underestimate of actual illness. The latest data set, covering 2011 to 2012, included 90 outbreaks resulting in
                    at least 1,788 cases of illness, 95 hospitalizations and one death. The majority (77%) of these cases were associated
                    with treated water, meaning venues like swimming pools and spas.
                </description>
                <updated>2015-02-14T15:52:34-06:00</updated>
            </item>
        </items>
    </category>
</source>