<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<source>
    <category id="1">
        <topic>Agriculture</topic>
        <items>

            <item>
                <link>https://www.ers.usda.gov/topics/farm-practices-management/irrigation-water-use</link>
                <title>Irrigation &amp; Water Use</title>
                <description>Agriculture is a major user of ground and surface water in the United States, accounting for
                    approximately 80 percent of the Nation's consumptive water use and over 90 percent in many Western States.
                    Efficient irrigation systems and water management practices can help maintain farm profitability in an era of
                    increasingly limited and more costly water supplies. Improved onfarm water management, combined with institutional
                    measures improving watershed-scale water-management, including the use of conserved water rights, dry-year water banks,
                    option water markets, and regulated irrigation withdrawals, may also reduce the impact of irrigated production
                    on offsite water quality while conserving water for growing nonagricultural demands.
                </description>
                <updated>2018-02-14T15:52:34-06:00</updated>
            </item>

            <item>
                <link>https://www.globalagriculture.org/report-topics/water.html</link>
                <title>Green and blue water</title>
                <description>When it comes to freshwater most people think of water in rivers and lakes, groundwater and glaciers,
                    the so-called “blue water”. Only part of the rainfall feeds this freshwater supply. The majority of rainfall comes down on
                    the Earth’s surface and either evaporates directly as “non-beneficial evaporation” or, after being used by plants,
                    as “productive transpiration”. This second type of rainwater is termed “green water”. The green water proportion of the
                    total available freshwater supply varies between 55% and 80%, depending on the region of the world, as well as local wood density.
                </description>
                <updated>2018-02-14T15:52:34-06:00</updated>
            </item>

            <item>
                <link>https://www.globalagriculture.org/report-topics/water.html</link>
                <title>Water</title>
                <description>Water is getting scarce – but what does this actually mean? After all, the planet never loses a single drop of H2O.
                    Although water is a finite resource, it will not be used up as long as we do not render it permanently unusable.
                    However, it is important to integrate human water usage into the natural hydrological cycle and to use the locally
                    available water in an adequate, effective, sustainable and fair way.
                </description>
                <updated>2018-02-14T15:52:34-06:00</updated>
            </item>
            <item>
                <link>http://moderator.droughtreporter.unl.edu/RSSfeed/ImpactView/44185</link>
                <title>Wheat crop stunted in Cape Girardeau, Missouri</title>
                <description>Dry conditions slowed crop planting and crop emergence in Cape Girardeau County, according to a
                    University of Missouri agronomy specialist. The wheat crop is shorter than that of one year ago, but is
                    uniform. The crops were described as brown, stunted, and stressed, but the crops were still alive.
                    Columbia Daily Tribune (Mo.), Feb. 12, 2018
                </description>
                <updated>2018-02-14T15:52:34-06:00</updated>
            </item>
        </items>
    </category>
    <category id="2">
        <topic>Industry</topic>
        <items>

            <item>
                <link>https://water.usgs.gov/edu/wuin.html</link>
                <title>Industrial water use</title>
                <description>
                  The industries that produce metals, wood and paper products, chemicals, gasoline and oils, and those
                    invaluable grabber utensils you use to get your ring out of the garbage disposal are major users of water.
                    Probably every manufactured product uses water during some part of the production process.
                    Industrial water use includes water used for such purposes as fabricating, processing, washing, diluting,
                    cooling, or transporting a product; incorporating water into a product; or for sanitation needs within
                    the manufacturing facility. Some industries that use large amounts of water produce such
                    commodities as food, paper, chemicals, refined petroleum, or primary metals.
                </description>
                <updated>2011-01-14T15:52:34-06:00</updated>
            </item>

            <item>
                <link>https://water.usgs.gov/edu/wateruse-total.html</link>
                <title>Total Water Use in the United States, 2010</title>
                <description>
                    The water in the Nation's rivers, lakes, reservoirs, and underground aquifers are vitally important
                    to our everyday life. These water bodies supply the water to serve the needs of every human and
                    for the world's ecological systems, too. Here in the United States, every 5 years the U.S.
                    Geological Survey (USGS) compiles county, state, and National water withdrawal and use data for
                    a number of water-use categories.
                </description>
                <updated>2011-02-14T15:52:34-06:00</updated>
            </item>
            <item>
                <link>http://moderator.droughtreporter.unl.edu/RSSfeed/ImpactView/44185</link>
                <title>Wheat crop stunted in Cape Girardeau, Missouri</title>
                <description>Dry conditions slowed crop planting and crop emergence in Cape Girardeau County, according to a
                    University of Missouri agronomy specialist. The wheat crop is shorter than that of one year ago, but is
                    uniform. The crops were described as brown, stunted, and stressed, but the crops were still alive.
                    Columbia Daily Tribune (Mo.), Feb. 12, 2018
                </description>
                <updated>2018-02-14T15:52:34-06:00</updated>
            </item>
        </items>
    </category>
     <category id="3">
        <topic>Domestic</topic>
        <items>
            <item>
                <link>https://water.usgs.gov/edu/wudo.html</link>
                <title>Domestic water use</title>
                <description>
                    Of course some of the most important uses for water are at our homes. Domestic water use is water
                    used for indoor and outdoor household purposes— all the things you do at home: drinking, preparing
                    food, bathing, washing clothes and dishes, brushing your teeth, watering the yard and garden,
                    and even washing the dog.
                </description>
                <updated>2018-02-14T15:52:34-06:00</updated>
            </item>

            <item>
                <link>https://www.epa.gov/watersense/how-we-use-water</link>
                <title>How We Use Water</title>
                <description>The Earth might seem like it has abundant water, but in fact less than 1 percent is available
                    for human use. The rest is either salt water found in oceans, fresh water frozen in the polar ice caps,
                    or too inaccessible for practical usage. While population and demand on freshwater resources are increasing,
                    supply will always remain constant. And although it's true that the water cycle continuously returns
                    water to Earth, it is not always returned to the same place, or in the same quantity and quality.
                </description>
                <updated>2018-02-14T15:52:34-06:00</updated>
            </item>
            <item>
                <link>http://moderator.droughtreporter.unl.edu/RSSfeed/ImpactView/44185</link>
                <title>Wheat crop stunted in Cape Girardeau, Missouri</title>
                <description>Dry conditions slowed crop planting and crop emergence in Cape Girardeau County, according to a
                    University of Missouri agronomy specialist. The wheat crop is shorter than that of one year ago, but is
                    uniform. The crops were described as brown, stunted, and stressed, but the crops were still alive.
                    Columbia Daily Tribune (Mo.), Feb. 12, 2018
                </description>
                <updated>2018-02-14T15:52:34-06:00</updated>
            </item>
        </items>
    </category>
</source>