<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<source>
    <category id="1">
        <topic>Ground water</topic>
        <items>
            <item>
                <link>https://environmenttexas.org/news/txe/texas-worst-unauthorized-industrial-water-pollution</link>
                <title>Texas worst for unauthorized industrial water pollution</title>
                <description>AUSTIN – 132 industrial facilities dumped excessive pollution into Texas waterways 938 times
                    over 21 months, more than any other state in the nation, according to a new report by
                    Environment Texas Research and Policy Center.  The facilities rarely faced penalties for this pollution
                    . AUSTIN Thursday, March 15, 2018
                </description>
                <updated>2018-02-14T15:52:34-06:00</updated>
            </item>
            <item>
                <link>http://www.ttuhub.net/water/2015/02/13/historic-water-sources-for-the-city-of-lubbock/</link>
                <title>Historic Water Sources for the City of Lubbock</title>
                <description>Throughout the years the city of Lubbock has had many different water sources.
                    Aubrey Spears, the city of Lubbock director of water utilities, said that with the Ogallala aquifer
                    being mined heavily for water, diversification of water resources was important.
                </description>
                <updated>2015-02-13T15:52:34-06:00</updated>
            </item>
            <item>
                <link>https://environmenttexas.org/news/txe/new-water-policies-can-cut-pollution-flooding-austin</link>
                <title>New Water Policies Can Cut Pollution and Flooding</title>
                <description>AUSTIN — Local environmental groups today announced their support for changes to Austin’s land
                    development code that will help reduce water pollution and flooding severity. The proposals will require
                    future developments to retain a minimum amount of rainwater with on-site features, and to limit the amount of runoff
                    flowing into the city’s drainage system. AUSTIN Tuesday, October 31, 2017
                </description>
                <updated>Tuesday, October 31, 2017</updated>
            </item>
            <item>
                <link>http://moderator.droughtreporter.unl.edu/RSSfeed/ImpactView/44185</link>
                <title>Wheat crop stunted in Cape Girardeau, Missouri</title>
                <description>Dry conditions slowed crop planting and crop emergence in Cape Girardeau County, according to a
                    University of Missouri agronomy specialist. The wheat crop is shorter than that of one year ago, but is
                    uniform. The crops were described as brown, stunted, and stressed, but the crops were still alive.
                    Columbia Daily Tribune (Mo.), Feb. 12, 2018
                </description>
                <updated>2018-02-14T15:52:34-06:00</updated>
            </item>

        </items>
    </category>
    <category id="2">
        <topic>Reservoir</topic>
        <items>
            <item>
                <link>https://ark.gamepedia.com/Water_Reservoir</link>
                <title>Water Reservoir</title>
                <description>The Water Reservoir is a standing storage device for containing water. It will act as a
                    temporary water source in case the irrigation network's normal water source is compromised in some way.
                    The reservoir can hold up to 200 water. It can't be filled up by connecting it to irrigation pipes,
                    but it automatically fills up during rain or snowfall. Because of this, it is extremely useful when
                    making new extremely inland bases, or bases up on mountainsides, as long as it is not undercover
                    from the rain.
                </description>
                <updated>2018-02-14T15:52:34-06:00</updated>
            </item>
            <item>
                <link>http://www.twdb.texas.gov/surfacewater/rivers/reservoirs/alan_henry/index.asp</link>
                <title>Alan Henry Reservoir (Brazos River Basin)</title>
                <description>Alan Henry Reservoir (also known as John T. Montford Dam and Lake Alan Henry) is located
                    about ten miles east of Justiceburg and about sixty-five miles southeast of the City of Lubbock,
                    on the border of Garza and Kent Counties, and is impounded on the South Fork of Double Mountain Fork
                    of the Brazos River, a tributary of the Brazos River.
                </description>
                <updated>2018-02-14T15:52:34-06:00</updated>
            </item>
            <item>
                <link>http://moderator.droughtreporter.unl.edu/RSSfeed/ImpactView/44185</link>
                <title>Wheat crop stunted in Cape Girardeau, Missouri</title>
                <description>Dry conditions slowed crop planting and crop emergence in Cape Girardeau County, according to a
                    University of Missouri agronomy specialist. The wheat crop is shorter than that of one year ago, but is
                    uniform. The crops were described as brown, stunted, and stressed, but the crops were still alive.
                    Columbia Daily Tribune (Mo.), Feb. 12, 2018
                </description>
                <updated>2018-02-14T15:52:34-06:00</updated>
            </item>
        </items>
    </category>
     <category id="3">
        <topic>Lake, River and Pond</topic>
        <items>
            <item>
                <link>http://moderator.droughtreporter.unl.edu/RSSfeed/ImpactView/44185</link>
                <title>Wheat crop stunted in Cape Girardeau, Missouri</title>
                <description>Dry conditions slowed crop planting and crop emergence in Cape Girardeau County, according to a
                    University of Missouri agronomy specialist. The wheat crop is shorter than that of one year ago, but is
                    uniform. The crops were described as brown, stunted, and stressed, but the crops were still alive.
                    Columbia Daily Tribune (Mo.), Feb. 12, 2018
                </description>
                <updated>2018-02-14T15:52:34-06:00</updated>
            </item>
            <item>
                <link>http://www.fao.org/docrep/u5835e/u5835e03.htm#2.2%20rivers</link>
                <title>Rivers</title>
                <description>Rivers are used all over the world as sources of irrigation water. The most typical quality
                    defining a river is that it flows, it is not a reservoir which contains a fixed amount of water.
                    At each moment a new amount of water is passing any given location along the river. The flow of river
                    fluctuates over time. The flows of some rivers fluctuate greatly over relatively short periods of time;
                    these are mainly small local rivers which respond quickly to rainfall in their catchment area.
                </description>
                <updated>2018-02-14T15:52:34-06:00</updated>
            </item>
            <item>
                <link>https://www.awwa.org/resources-tools/public-affairs/public-affairs-events/drinking-water-week.aspx</link>
                <title>Drinking water</title>
                <description>For more than 40 years the American Water Works Association and its members have celebrated
                    Drinking Water Week – a unique opportunity for both water professionals and the communities they
                    serve to join together in recognizing the vital role water plays in our daily lives. Drinking Water
                    Week is celebrated the first full week in May each year. Please join AWWA as we celebrate drinking water!
                </description>
                <updated>2018-02-14T15:52:34-06:00</updated>
            </item>
            <item>
                <link>https://www.awwa.org/resources-tools/water-knowledge/source-water-protection.aspx</link>
                <title>Communicating Source Water Protection Efforts in Consumer Confidence Reports</title>
                <description>Outreach to and education of the general public are critical components of source water protection.
                    This targeted literature review examined how utilities of all sizes are currently using their Consumer
                    Confidence Reports (CCRs) to educate customers about source water protection needs and efforts.
                </description>
                <updated>2018-02-14T15:52:34-06:00</updated>
            </item>

        </items>
    </category>
</source>